

CONTACT



813-391-3420



pmanecci@gmail.com



Groveland, FL



https://pmanecci.github.io /pm-portfolio/

CODING LANGUAGES

- HTML/CSS
- Bootstrap & Bulma Frameworks
- JavaScript
- React
- Express.js & Node.js
- MySQL & Mongo
- Git/Github

SOFT SKILLS

- Effective Communication
- · Problem Solving
- Process Improvement
- Adaptability
- Time Management
- Attention to Detail

LEADERSHIP/ AWARDS

- IPD Facilitator 6th Grade Math
- · Team Lead
- NJHS Advisor
- Rookie Teacher of the Year: 2020-21

REFERENCE

KATIE TRACY

Principal, Florida Virtual School ktracy@flvs.net

WILLIAM ROBERTS

Principal, Windy Hill Middle School robertsw@lake.k12.fl.us

PATTY MANECCI

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SUMMARY

I am a qualified professional with over 10 years of instructional and administrative experience seeking opportunities to apply my natural aptitude for problem-solving, attention to detail and love of learning to creating and coding awesome web applications!

EXPERIENCE

6TH GRADE MATHEMATICS INSTRUCTOR

Florida Virtual School

2020 - Present

- Responsible for providing direct and meaningful communication, feedback, instruction and technical support for a classroom of 80-155 6th Grade math students and their families
- Utilized HTML/CSS to enhance plain text grading feedback and embed images, videos, and links to maximize engagement and user experience
- Employ strategic time management strategies to maximize efficiency in a fully remote work environment
- Utilized Google Slides Embed feature to create individualized pace plans for tracking assignments and work for each student

6TH GRADE MATHEMATICS INSTRUCTOR

Lake County Schools: Windy Hill Middle School

2017-2020

- · Anticipated user experience and revised projects and products as needed to decrease customer friction and regularly created and built new resources to meet the needs of multiple learning modes
- Established and maintained a data management system for individual grading/behavior management, team initiatives, and timely and targeted communication with all stakeholders
- Lead monthly full-day instructional strategic planning sessions for the 6th Grade Math Department and developed and delivered continuing education credit presentations on District-Wide professional development days.

EDUCATION

2021-2022

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA Coding Bootcamp: Full-Stack Development

2006-2010

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

Bachelor of Science: Event & Hospitality Management